<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>SibTech, Inc.</title>
    <link>http://sibtech.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on SibTech, Inc.</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://sibtech.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The focus of our company is optimization of biopharmaceutical proteins for multiple applications, such as targeted drug delivery, targeted imaging, and derivatization of biomedical surfaces. Our work is based on a platform technology for converting proteins into a format suitable for site-specific conjugation of various payloads. For this, proteins are expressed with a fusion Cys-tag, a 15-aa cysteine-containing peptide, whose thiol group is used for site-specific modifications. Our experience with different Cys-tagged proteins and very diverse payloads suggests that virtually every protein can be Cys-tagged and made to carry a payload without loss of functional activity. Thus, our approach allows rapid development of new applications for existing and emerging biopharmaceutical proteins, as well as modifying them for superior pharmacokinetic and formulation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To date, our technology yielded the first candidate for clinical development, a proprietary Cys-tagged single-chain vascular endothelial growth factor (scVEGF) derivatized with a contrast agent for PET imaging of VEGF receptors. These receptors play a pivotal role in tumor angiogenesis and their inhibition is the major goal of anti-angiogenic therapies. We believe that imaging VEGF receptors in tumor vasculature can provide crucial information for early diagnostics, development and monitoring therapeutic regimens, and rational patient selection for complex and very expensive treatments. Currently, there are no contrast agents for imaging VEGF receptors and our lead candidate is being developed to satisfy this unmet need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SibTech is currently looking for business partnerships and scientific collaboration with industrial and academic groups seeking to expand the use of existing and emerging biopharmaceutical proteins.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Information</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For more information, please contact:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dr. Joseph M. Backer&lt;br/&gt;
Chief Executive Officer&lt;br/&gt;
SibTech, Inc.&lt;br/&gt;
115A Commerce dr.&lt;br/&gt;
Brookfield, CT 06804&lt;br/&gt;
Phone: +1 203-775-5677&lt;br/&gt;
Fax: +1 203-775-5705&lt;br/&gt;
E-mail: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jbacker@sibtech.com&#34;&gt;jbacker@sibtech.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Licensing</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/licensing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/licensing/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;The following technologies are available for licensing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Call +1 203-775-5677 or email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jbacker@sibtech.com&#34;&gt;jbacker@sibtech.com&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;i-new-fusion-tag-for-site-specific-conjugation-of-payloads-to-targeting-proteins&#34;&gt;I. New fusion tag for site-specific conjugation of payloads to targeting proteins.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;description&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Targeted delivery of therapeutic and diagnostic agents might significantly decrease systemic toxicity, increase efficacy of new and old drugs, support development of personalized medicine, and provide new uses for existing therapeutic proteins. Although many proteins can be used for targeted delivery, random conjugation of a &amp;ldquo;payload&amp;rdquo; to a protein creates heterogeneous products that are not well-suited for development and for regulatory approval. This invention eliminates random conjugation and provides a strategy for development of functionally active, homogeneous protein-based products. In this strategy, a protein is expressed with a humanized 15-aa cysteine-containing tag (Cys-tag), and a payload is site-specifically conjugated to a cysteine residue in Cys-tag via thiol-directed chemistries. Cys-tag is compatible with every protein tested so far, and accommodates payloads as different as drugs, contrast agents, dendrimers, liposomes, and functional proteins.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;benefits-and-application&#34;&gt;Benefits and Application&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein can be used for targeted delivery of therapeutic and diagnostic agents, dramatically expanding the field of use for a given protein therapeutic.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein can be used in development of protein therapeutics to establish biodistribution and internalization.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein can be modified to alter pharmacokinetic via site-specific pegylation.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein can be modified to suit specific formulation, for example, slow-release formulations.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein can be conjugated to tissue engineering scaffolds, biomedical surfaces, or nanoparticles, providing uniform protein-derivatized constructs.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;intellectual-property-status&#34;&gt;Intellectual Property Status&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US patent 7,355,019 B2 issued 04/08/2008.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;related-publication&#34;&gt;Related Publication&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/papers/VEGF_BD_Mol_Cancer_Ther.pdf&#34;&gt;Mol. Cancer. Ther. 4, 1423-1429, 2005&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/papers/Blankenberg_2006.pdf&#34;&gt;Europ. J. Nucl. Med. Mol. Imag. 33, 841-848, 2006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/papers/Wu_2006.pdf&#34;&gt;Anti-Cancer Agents Med. Chem. 6, 167-184, 2006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/papers/Backer_2006b.pdf&#34;&gt;Bioconjugate Chem., 17, 912-919, 2006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/papers/Backer_2006a.pdf&#34;&gt;Biomaterials 27, 5452-5458, 2006&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;ii-novel-agents-for-imaging-receptors-for-vascular-endothelial-growth-factor&#34;&gt;II. Novel agents for imaging receptors for vascular endothelial growth factor.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;description-1&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF) is the key regulator of angiogenesis and overexpressed VEGF receptors play the crucial role in the onset and progression of tumor angiogenesis. receptors are the primary targets of tremendous efforts to develop inhibitors of angiogenesis. However, these receptors are not used as biomarkers for prescribing or monitoring anti-angiogenic therapy due to a lack of methods for assessment of their prevalence. This invention provides molecular probes for PET, SPECT, and NIRF imaging VEGF receptors. The probes are based on a novel single-chain VEGF (scVEGF) expressed with a proprietary cysteine-containing tag for site-specific conjugation of contrast agents. VEGF-based probes bind to and internalized by VEGF receptors as effectively as parental VEGF, providing unique opportunities for non-invasive imaging VEGF receptors in vivo. Information on prevalence of VEGF receptors in patients might lead to evidence-based selection of candidates for anti-angiogenic therapy, facilitate design of personalized treatment regiments, enable early diagnostics and discrimination between benign and malignant lesions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;benefits-and-application-1&#34;&gt;Benefits and Application&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Clinical development of VEGF based probes for PET imaging will lead to a new diagnostic tool for a wide range of indications.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;VEGF-based imaging probes are powerful tools in R&amp;amp;D on drugs affecting vasculature&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;intellectual-property-status-1&#34;&gt;Intellectual Property Status&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;US patent 7,355,019 B2 issued 04/08/2008.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;related-publication-1&#34;&gt;Related Publication&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Mol. Cancer. Ther. 4, 1423-1429, 2005&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Europ. J. Nucl. Med. Mol. Imag. 33, 841-848, 2006&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nature Med 13, 504-509, 2007&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;
Call +1 203-775-5677 or email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:jbacker@sibtech.com&#34;&gt;jbacker@sibtech.com&lt;/a&gt; for additional information.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Optimization of Proteins for Multiple Applications</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/conjugates/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/conjugates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;SibTech provides Custom Protein Optimization Service, which is rapid, flexible, and comprehensive. It includes the following stages:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol id=&#34;cp_optimization_stages&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Your protein is re-engineered for expression with N- or C-terminal Cys-tag.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Cys-tagged protein is expressed, refolded, purified, and tested for functional activities in vitro.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A payload you need is site-specifically conjugated to Cys-tagged protein. We are confident in our ability to conjugate virtually any payload. Our menu of standard payloads includes:
    &lt;ol id=&#34;standard_payloads&#34;&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Fluorescent dyes for in vivo and in vitro targeted imaging&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Radionuclide chelator for SPECT targeted imaging&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Radionuclide chelator for PET targeted imaging&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Lipids for formulation into liposomes or other lipid-based formulations&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;PEG for extending clearance time&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;Other proteins, such as those used in tissue scaffold, implant, or biosensors engineering&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Conjugates are purified and tested for functional activities in vitro.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If necessary, adapter-based conjugates are made for self-assembly with your Cys-tagged protein.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In our experience, a new conjugate can be made and validated &lt;i&gt;in vitro&lt;/i&gt; in 2 to 4 months. At that point you would have a powerful R&amp;amp;D tool, for example, for targeted imaging. The new conjugate is then evaluated &lt;i&gt;in vivo&lt;/i&gt;, for a rational decision regarding development of your protein for new clinical application(s).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our Science</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/science/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/platform&#34;&gt;Technology Platform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/publications&#34;&gt;Recent Publications&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/posters&#34;&gt;Recent Posters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our recent posters</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/posters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/posters/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/presentations/Imaging_CRS-2006.ppt&#34;&gt;Molecular Imaging of VEGF Receptors in Angiogenic Vasculature with Single-chain VEGF Driven Probes (July 22-26, 2006. 33rd Annual Meeting of the Controlled Release Society. Vienna, Austria)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/presentations/Surface_immobilization_CRS-2006.ppt&#34;&gt;A New Technology for Site-Specific Conjugation of Cytokines to Surfaces.&lt;br /&gt;
Effects of Signaling by Fibronectin-Conjugated Single-Chain VEGF on VEGFR-2 Positive Cells. (July 22-26, 2006. 33rd Annual Meeting of the Controlled Release Society. Vienna, Austria)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/presentations/Targeting_Dox_Liposomes_to_Tumor_Vasculature_45x45.ppt&#34;&gt;Using VEGF for Targeting Doxorubicin-loaded Liposomes to Tumor Vasculature. (June 18-22, 2005. 32nd Annual Meeting of the Controlled Release Society. Miami Beach, Fl.)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/presentations/Cysteine_tag_SMI-2005.ppt&#34;&gt;A Cysteine-containing Tag and a Complimentary Adapter Protein for Loading Contrast Agents Onto Targeting Proteins. (Sept. 7-10, 2005. The Society for Molecular Imaging Fourth Annual Meeting. Cologne, Germany)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our recent publications</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/publications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tedesco MM, Terashima M, Blankenberg FG, Levashova Z, Spin JM, Backer M, Backer J, Sho M, Sho E, McConnell MV, Dalman RL. (2009) Expression During Experimental Aortic Aneurysm Progression Analysis of In Situ and Ex Vivo Vascular Endothelial Growth Factor Receptor Arterioscler. Thromb. Vasc. Biol. DOI:10.1161/ATVBAHA.109.187757.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Levashova Z, Backer M, Horng G, Felsher D, Backer JM, Blankenberg FG (2009). SPECT and PET Imaging of EGF Receptors with Site-Specifically Labeled EGF and Dimeric EGF. Bioconjug. Chem. 20, 742–749.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saban R, Saban MR, Maier J, Fowler B, Tengowski M, Davis CA, Wu XR, Culkin DJ, Hauser P, Backer J, Hurst RE. (2008) Urothelial expression of Neuropilins and VEGF receptors in control and interstitial cystitis patients.American Journal of Physiology - Renal Physiology. 295(6):F1613-23, 2008&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saban MR, Backer JM, Backer MV, Maier J, Fowler B, Davis CA, Simpson C, Wu X-R, Birder L, Freeman MR, Soker S, and Saban R (2008). VEGF receptors and neuropilins are expressed in the urothelial and neuronal cells in normal mouse urinary bladder and are up-regulated in inflammation. Am. J. Physiol. Renal. 295(1):F60-72.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Levenson RM, Lynch DT, Kobayashi H, Backer JM, and Backer MV (2008) Multiplexing with multispectral imaging: from mice to microscopy. ILAR J. 49, 78-87&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Levashova Z, Backer M, Backer JM, Blankenberg FG (2008). Direct site-specific labeling of the Cys-tag moiety in scVEGF with Technetium 99m. Bioconjugate Chem. 19, 1049-1054&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer MV, Levashova Z, Levenson R, Blankenberg FG, Backer JM. (2008) Cysteine-containing fusion tag for site-specific conjugation of therapeutic and imaging agents to targeting proteins. Methods in Molecular Medicine. Peptide-based Drug Design. Humana Press, New York, NY. Ed: L. Otvos. Vol. 494, p.275-94.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nature.com/nm/journal/v13/n4/abs/nm1522.html&#34;&gt;Backer MV, Levashova Z, Patel V, Jehning BT, Claffey K, Blankenberg FG, and Backer JM (2007) Molecular imaging of VEGF receptors in angiogenic vasculature with single-chain VEGF driven probes Nature Medicine, 13, 504-509.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V., Patel, V., Jehning, B. T., Claffey, K., Karginov, V. A. and Backer, J.M. (2007b) Inhibition of anthrax protective antigen outside and inside the cell. Antimicrob. Agent. Chemother. 51, 245-251.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blankenberg, F.G., Backer, M. V., Levashova, Z., Vimalkumar Patel, V., and Backer, J.M. (2006) In vivo tumor angiogenesis imaging with site-specific labeled 99mTc-HYNIC-VEGF. Eur. J. Nucl. Med. Mol. Imag. 33, 841-848.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V., Patel, V., Jehning, B. T., Claffey, K., and Backer, J.M. (2006a) Surface immobilization of active vascular endothelial growth factor via a cysteine-containing tag. Biomaterials 27, 5452-5458.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thirumamagal, B. T. S., Zhao, X. B., Bandyopadhyaya, A. K., Narayanasamy, S., Johnsamuel, J., Tiwari, R., Golightly, D. W., Patel, V., Jehning, B. T., Backer, M. V., Barth, R. F., Lee, R. J., Backer, J. M., and Tjarks, W. Receptor-targeted liposomal delivery of boron-containing cholesterol mimics for boron neutron capture therapy (BNCT). Bioconjugate Chem. (2006) DOI 10.1021/bc060075 (on line 8.15.2006).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wu, G., Barth, R., Yang, W., Lee, R. J., Tjarks W., Backer, M.V., and Backer, J.M. (2006), Boron containing macromolecules and nanovehicles as delivery agents for neutron capture therapy. Anti-Cancer Agents Med. Chem. 6, 167-184.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M.V. Patel, V., Jehning, B., and Backer, J.M. (2006b) Self-Assembled “Dock and Lock” system for linking payloads to targeting proteins. Bioconjugate Chem. 17, 912-919.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M.V., Gaynutdinov, T.I., Patel V., Bandyopadhyaya A.K., Thirumamagal, B.T.S, Tjarks W., Barth, R., Claffey, K.P., and Backer, J.M. (2005) Vascular endothelial growth factor selectively targets boronated dendrimers to tumor vasculature. Mol. Cancer Ther. 4, 1423-1429.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V., Elliot, J., Gaynutdinov, T. I., and Backer, J. M. (2004a) Assembly of targeting complexes driven by a single-chain antibody. J. Immunol. Meth. 289, 37-45.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blankenberg, F. G., Mandl, S., Cao, Y.-A., O’Connell-Rodwell, C., Contag, C., Mari, C., Gaynutdinov, T. I., Vanderheyden, J.-L., Backer, M. V., and M. Backer, J. M. (2004) Tumor imaging using a standardized radiolabeled adapter protein docked to vascular endothelial growth factor (VEGF). J. Nuclear Med. 45, 1373-1380.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V., Gaynutdinov, T., Patel, V., Jehning, B., Myshkin, E., and Backer, J. (2004) Adapter protein for site-specific conjugation of payloads for targeted drug delivery. Bioconj. Chem. 15, 1021-1029.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. Gaynutdinov, T., Gorshkova, I., Crouch, R., Hu, T., Aloise, R., Arab, M., Przekop, K., and Backer, J. (2003) Humanized docking system for assembly of targeting drug delivery complexes. J. Controlled Release 89, 499-511.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaynutdinov, T., Myshkin, E., Backer, J., and Backer, M. (2003) Chimeric ribonuclease as a source of human adapter protein for targeted drug delivery. Prot. Eng. 16, 771-775.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M., Aloise, R., Przekop, K., Stoletov, K., and Backer, J. (2002) Molecular vehicles for targeted drug delivery. Bioconjugate Chem. 13, 462-467.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M., Gaynutdinov, T., Aloise, R., Przekop, K., and Backer, J. (2002) Engineering S-protein fragments of bovine ribonuclease A for targeted drug delivery. Prot. Exp. Purif. 26, 455-461.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V. and Backer, J. M. (2001) Functionally active VEGF fusion proteins. Prot. Exp. Purif. 23, 1-7.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Gaidamakova, E. K., Backer, M. V., and Backer, J. M. (2001) Molecular vehicle for target-mediated delivery of therapeutics and diagnostics. J. Control. Release 74, 341-347.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V. Budker, V. G., and Backer, J. M. (2001) Shiga-like toxin-VEGF fusion are selectively cytotoxic to endothelial cells overexpressing VEGFR-2. J. Control. Release 74, 349-355.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Backer, M. V. and Backer, J. M. (2001a) Targeting endothelial cells overexpressing VEGFR-2: selective toxicity of Shiga-like toxin-VEGF fusion proteins. Bioconjugate Chem. 12, 1066-1073.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products for Research</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/products/</guid>
      <description>&lt;table class=&#34;product&#34;&gt;
    &lt;thead&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;New Catalog #&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Description&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;Packing&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;Price, $&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/thead&gt;
    &lt;tbody&gt;
        &lt;tr class=&#34;sectionheader&#34;&gt;
            &lt;td colspan=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Mammalian cell lines&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT021-293&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;293/KDR &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT021-293R&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;293/KDR-Rluc&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT021-293F&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;293/KDR-Fc&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT021-PAE&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;PAE/KDR&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT000-PAE&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;PAE &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$500&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT024-293&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;293/TEM-8&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT024-CHO&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;CHO/TEM-8&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT093-4T1&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;4T1Luc &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT093-4T1V&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;4T1lucV165&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT093-MDA &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;MDA231/Luc  &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;1 vial&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;

        &lt;tr class=&#34;sectionheader&#34;&gt;
            &lt;td colspan=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Recombinant proteins expressed with Cys-tag&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT301_scVEGF.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT301&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;scVEGF, single-chain vascular endothelial growth factor&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT301-IN_Inactivated_scVEGF.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT301-IN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated scVEGF&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$650&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT300_Deprotected_C4-Monothiol_scVEGF.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT300&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;[C4]-Monothiol scVEGF &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$800&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT300-IN&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated [C4]-Monothiol scVEGF&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$850&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT201_ctEGF.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT201&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;ctEGF, Human epidermal growth factor&lt;br/&gt;Old name: Cys-EGF, Human epidermal growth factor)&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$600&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT200_Deprotected_ctEGF.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT200&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;[C4]-Monothiol ctEGF&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$800&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT101&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;dEGF, &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.2 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT501_ctFlex.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT501&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;ctFlex,  Extracellular domain of human FLT3 ligand&lt;br/&gt;Old name: Cys-Flex, Extracellular domain of human FLT3 ligand&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$800&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT901_LFn-ct.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT901&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;LFn-ct, 1-124aa catalytically inactive fragment of anthrax lethal factor&lt;br/&gt;Old name:Cys-LFn, 1-124aa catalytically inactive fragment of anthrax lethal factor&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$800&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;

        &lt;tr class=&#34;sectionheader&#34;&gt;
            &lt;td colspan=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Chimeric toxins&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT071-013&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;SLT-VEGF&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT077-012&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;EGF-SubA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT076-012&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;EGF-SLT&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.1 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;

        &lt;tr class=&#34;sectionheader&#34;&gt;
            &lt;td colspan=&#34;4&#34;&gt;Protein conjugates&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT302_scVEGF-Si.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT302&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;scVEGF/Si, near-infrared fluorescent tracer for imaging VEGF receptors.&lt;/p&gt;
                &lt;p&gt;scVEGF site-specifically modified with other fluorescent dyes is available upon request.&lt;/p&gt;
            &lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT302-IN_Inactivated_scVEGF-Si.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT302-IN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated scVEGF/Si for assessment of non-receptor mediated scVEGF/Si uptake&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$950&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT304_scVEGF-HYNIC.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT304&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;scVEGF/HYNIC&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT304-IN_Inactivated_scVEGF-HYNIC.docx&#34;&gt;SBT304-IN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated scVEGF/HYNIC&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$950&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT335_scVEGF-PEG-DOTA.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT335&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;scVEGF-PEG-DOTA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT335-IN_Inactivated_scVEGF-PEG-DOTA.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT335-IN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated scVEGF-PEG-DOTA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$950&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;SBT336&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;scVEGF-PEG-NOTA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT336-IN_Inactivated_scVEGF-PEG-NOTA.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT336-IN&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;Inactivated scVEGF-PEG-NOTA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$950&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT309_scVEGF-biotin.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT309&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;scVEGF/biotin&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT202_ctEGF-Si.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT202&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;ctEGF/Si, near-infrared fluorescent tracer for imaging EGF receptors&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
        &lt;tr&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pnumber&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/certificates/SBT235_ctEGF-PEG-DOTA.pdf&#34;&gt;SBT235&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;pname&#34;&gt;ctEGF-PEG-DOTA&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;quantity&#34;&gt;0.15 mg&lt;/td&gt;
            &lt;td class=&#34;price&#34;&gt;$900&lt;/td&gt;
        &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To order our products, please e-mail your purchase order to &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:info@sibtech.com&#34;&gt;info@sibtech.com&lt;/a&gt;, or fax it to +1 203-775-5705, or call +1 203-775-5677.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology Platform: Making Protein Work</title>
      <link>http://sibtech.com/platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://sibtech.com/platform/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The majority of biopharmaceutical proteins are used &amp;quot;as is&amp;quot;. However, the use of existing and emerging biopharmaceutical proteins can be greatly expanded, if they are derivatized with useful payloads. The resulting conjugates can be used for targeted delivery of therapeutic and diagnostic agents, development of protein-derivatized biomedical surfaces and scaffolds, and for optimization of protein formulation and pharmacokinetic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the progress in this field has been very slow. The fundamental problem has been the lack of an efficient technology for making protein-based conjugates. Most often conjugation relies on a random chemical cross-linking of a payload directly to a protein. Such process yields a mixture of products with varying activity, biodistribution, and pharmacokinetic. Alternatively, a cysteine residue is engineered into a &amp;quot;safe&amp;quot; position in the protein and its thiol group is used for site-specific cross-linking. However, the latter approach requires sophisticated protein engineering that is customized for every protein.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To expand the use of biopharmaceutical proteins, SibTech developed a platform technology for site-specific payload conjugation. In our approach, a protein is expressed with N- or C-terminal Cys-tag, a 15-aa, cysteine-containing fusion tag, whose unique thiol group is used for conjugation (Fig. 1). Cys-tag (KESCAKKFQRQHMDS) is a fragment of human RNase I with single amino acid substitution, and therefore it is not expected to be particularly immunogenic in humans. Remarkably, Cys-tag does not interfere with recombinant protein refolding and formation of native disulfide bonds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;labeled_image_1&#34;&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;http://sibtech.com/images/delivery/uniform-conjugates-fig1.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Figure 1&#34;/&gt;

&lt;div class=&#34;img_label&#34;&gt;

&lt;b&gt;Figure 1. Cys-tagged Proteins for Multiple Applications.&lt;/b&gt; Site-specific conjugation via Cys-tag creates new uniform protein-based products.
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;clear: both;&#34;&gt;
Once Cys-tagged protein is expressed, it can be used for conjugation of a variety of payloads. To date, we have expressed a number of recombinant proteins with either N- or C-terminal Cys-tag. These proteins were derivatized with payloads as diverse as radionuclide chelators for &lt;i&gt;in vivo&lt;/i&gt; imaging (Blankenberg et al., 2006, &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.nature.com/nm/journal/v13/n4/abs/nm1522.html&#34;&gt;Backer et al., 2007a&lt;/a&gt;), high capacity drug carriers, such as nanoparticles, dendrimers (Backer et al, 2005), liposomes (Thirumamagal et al., 2006, Backer et al., 2007b), fibronectin for derivatization of biomedical surfaces (Backer et al., 2006a), or polyethylenglycol and lipids for improving pharmacokinetic and formulation. In majority of cases, conjugates retained functional activity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For &amp;quot;difficult&amp;quot; payloads, which inhibit protein activity when attached directly to Cys-tag, SibTech developed a &amp;quot;Dock &amp;amp; Lock&amp;quot; system based on a complimentary humanized adapter protein (Fig. 2). Adapter protein is designed to bind to Cys-tag and then the complex is &amp;quot;locked&amp;quot; via a disulfide bond formed between complimentary cysteine residues in Cys-tag and adapter (Backer et al., 2006b). Thus, when necessary, a payload is conjugated to adapter and then this conjugate is  &amp;quot;Docked &amp;amp; Locked&amp;quot; to any protein expressed with Cys-tag (Fig. 2).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div id=&#34;labeled_image_2&#34;&gt;

&lt;img src=&#34;http://sibtech.com/images/delivery/conjugates-via-adapter-fig2.gif&#34; alt=&#34;Figure 2&#34;/&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;img_label&#34;&gt;
&lt;b&gt;Figure 2. Self-Assembled Conjugates of Cys-tagged Proteins.&lt;/b&gt; Pre-made adapter-payload conjugate is &amp;quot;docked and locked&amp;quot; to Cys-tagged protein.

&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;clear: both;&#34;&gt;
We are confident that the majority of existing and emerging biopharmaceutical proteins can be readily expressed with Cys-tag, derivatized with payloads, and tested in vitro and in vivo to establish feasibility of new applications. We look forward to working with industrial and academic groups that are interested in expanding the use of their proteins (see, &lt;a href=&#34;http://sibtech.com/conjugates&#34;&gt;Custom Conjugates&lt;/a&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>